https://www.sportknows.net/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy is important to us and we have added this privacy page, to explain a few quick things about the site and what info we collect, which is not much at all.
What Info Do We Collect and Why?
Whenever you comment on this blog you will be required to leave your email address. We only collect this so we can email you about your comment if need be. However if you leave your name and email in the opt-in form box, you will then be sent a confirmation email from Aweber, and if you click that, then your email will be moved to my Aweber email marketing list, so I can send you important updates. We will never ever sell your contact info or give it away to anyone, period!!
Cookies
This blog uses a technology known as “cookies” and web server log files to collect info, such as date and time of your visit, what pages you looked at and the time you spent on each page, etc..
Copyright
Under no circumstance can any content on this website be copied or reproduced in any way. This includes any of the reviews and videos that are hosted on the domain, SportKnows.net. If any person or company does use the owner of this websites name, video, or blog content without getting written consent from the site then legal action may be undertaken against the offending parties.
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?
As you visit and browse our Website, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Website and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies.
IP Addresses
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.
Sharing and Selling Information
We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.
How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at the usual address.
What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the Public.
What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Website or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.
Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including web sites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.
Your Consent
By using our Website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out
This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.
A Special Note About Children
Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 14) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.
Acquisition or Changes in Ownership
In the event that the website (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.
Policy Modifications
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.
Last Edited Oct 13, 2018
If you require any other information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us here without any hesitation.
Recommended For YouBest Scuba Air Tanks – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Inflatable Kayaks – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Boxing Punching Bags – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Climbing Ascenders – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Ping Pong Net – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Water Polo Net – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Ping Pong Paddles – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Tennis Ankle Braces – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Water Polo Balls – Buyer’s Guide And ReviewBest Running Armbands – Buyer’s Guide And Review
Popular SportsArchery
Badminton
Baseball
Billiard
Bowling
Boxing
Carrom
Climbing
Amazon Affiliate Disclosure - Contact Us - Privacy Policy - Terms Of Services - Copyrights@ Sport Knows - All Rights Reserved.
Top
